Now that you know how to create an
arbitrarily complex nested layout, it's important to understand
that they don't come for free. Once again,
the resource constraints of the platform spoil the party.
[SOUND] Inflating complex layouts can be expensive, potentially
impacting the performance and responsiveness of your app.
So there are two good rules of thumb
to help. First, keep your layout shallow and wide,
rather than deep and narrow. That means you're better
off with more siblings and fewer children. Because it's
never as simple as that, you also want to
avoid having excessive views. In the most general terms, that
means your activities' full hierarchy should never have more
than ten nested views or over 80 views in
total. That probably sounds like a lot, but let's
open up the Hierarchy Viewer tool in Android studio and
see just how quickly that can add up